Wow. that looks dangerous.
It is dangerous.
But there's a beauty to it.
60-40 with a 30% promoter
off the top.
I don't loan to lose.
That sounds like a good deal.
We're not done
negotiating yet. Cami.
We're done now.
It's my new goal in life. Tommy.
to have you trust me.
Should take me back to the home.
This ain't working.
Did he know Mama?
Did he call her an addict
or something?
'Cause it's true.
How much
do engagement rings cost?
You know what.
you come by the house. I'm gonna
give you my engagement ring.
You understand that
a romantic relationship
with an M-TEX employee
violates the stipulations
of your contract?
You can be good at your job
and enjoy yourself.
You know that. right?
Your grump of a son won't
dance with me.
I guess I got a dance or two
left in me.
My father's story's over.
Doesn't look like it's over.
You know. I get
the sense she don't trust you.
She thinks I'm gonna
lose her fortune.
Well. you're gonna have to
do something about that.
Because when those sharks
smell her doubting you.
they're gonna poison her
with reason to get rid of you.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Uh. who the fuck are you?
- Waitress.
waitress!
Don't rape me!
I'm not gonna rape you.
The fuck's wrong with you?
Tommy. put your dick away.
Don't be scared. darling.
That wasn't about you.
He eats Cialis like M&M's.
runs into door jams
all morning with that thing.
Son of a bitch.
So sorry about that.
- Oh.
- Okay. just leave the tray.
Uh. thank you.
Go ahead.
Nice.
What are you doing.
sneaking fucking
hotel workers in here for?
I was trying to surprise you
with breakfast in bed.
Well. you sure as shit did.
That is not the best angle
of your ball sack. I might add.
I'd scream. too.
You know.
you've really got to love a man
to look at him from there.
Poor thing.
If she wasn't a lesbian
when she walked in here.
she's a fucking lesbian now.
Where you going?
Getting dressed.
When my husband
flashes the waitstaff.
it kind of kills the mood.
Well. honey.
you're the one that told me
to take
an extra pill last night.
Now what do I do
with this fucking thing? Huh?
Why don't you
fuck one of those waffles?
Okay. maybe I will.
Matter of fact. I might fuck
the whole breakfast.
The waffles and the fruit
and the goddamn bagel
and the omelet.
Don't you fucking
touch my omelet.
Oh. the omelet's the first thing
that's getting fucked.
Don't you fuck my omelet.
You better order another one
because it's fucked.
Way to ruin the weekend. Tommy.
The weekend just started. babe.
And you already ruined it.
Buenos días.
Mm. Buen día a ti.
¿Dormiste bien?
I did.
Why are we speaking Spanish?
I've been practicing.
I can see that.
Well. I just figured.
it's your first language.
I should know how to speak it.
And when you start talking shit.
I'll know what you're saying.
Do you know French?
- No.
- Hmm.
Guess I better learn that then.
It's important I'm able
to talk shit about you
without repercussions.
It's the corner shop
of any healthy relationship.
"Cornerstone." babe.
Oye. no necesito
que corrijas cada palabra
que uso mal.
Okay. what does that mean?
Looks like I don't have
to learn French for a while.
How was Isabel?
Isabel was a trap.
Did you survive it?
She taught me how to make salsa.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Salsa roja or verde?
Both.
Mm.
You did more than survive.
Two down. one to go.
Mm. You're on the clock. flaco.
Don't make me wait forever.
I want it
to be special when I ask.
Having done this once before.
the asking isn't
what makes it special.
The wedding doesn't either.
The wedding's for everyone else.
We make the marriage special.
We make
every day special. Cooper.
And it's
a lot harder than it sounds.
Understand?
I'm trying really hard
to listen.
but you're naked and
it's got my brain
pretty jumbled.
Men.
Morning.
Morning. You hungry?
Um...
I...
No? Not a breakfast eater?
No. I...
I have breakfast.
It's typically
- a juice blend...
- Uh-huh.
Some yogurt.
açaí. blueberries.
if they're wild.
Well. we don't have any of that.
What do we have?
Coffee?
Sure.
Barefoot.
That's really living
on the edge in West Texas.
- Dirt feels good.
- Oh. yeah?
Till it doesn't.
When something under you
stings the shit out of you.
When I overcome my shame.
I'll need some help
understanding the mechanics
of the travel trailer toilet.
Well. the pedal is on the floor.
It's like a car.
Below the seat.
you push it halfway down.
it fills the basin.
All the way down flushes it.
Thank you. How about the shower?
There's no pedals in the shower.
It's just like the one
you got at home.
you know. just probably...
probably much smaller.
I'll assume.
God. it's beautiful. isn't it?
That's not the word
I would use to describe it.
You know that its formation
is a result of tectonic events
a billion or more years ago.
You know. we're sitting
right now on a shallow sea.
And there was this massive
evaporative event.
and then this became
an inland sea.
connected down to the ocean by
what we call the Hovey Channel.
formed during the
Permian period. hence the name.
There was massive marine life
in this sea. massive.
And that marine life is now
the oil we all seek today.
We're eating breakfast
on the ocean floor.
Isn't that something?
Yeah.
And you?
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- A lawyer.
Mm-hmm.
So. you like to fight.
I like to beat people
who underestimate me.
Underestimate you?
Which is everyone.
Who underestimates you?
I mean. y-you scare
the shit out of me.
You're smart. you're beautiful.
you got a chip
on your shoulder the size
of this drilling rig here.
You don't act very scared.
I like to overcome my fears.
Oh. is that
what you've been doing?
You know what.
I'm a big believer
in only getting involved
with women way out of my league.
Ah.
Okay. And why is that?
If you don't feel like
you deserve what you got.
you'll always work hard
to deserve it.
- What?
- Wow. Okay.
You know. I bet the ladies
really lap that shit up.
Well. I've never actually
been with a woman
way out of my league till you.
so this is the first test
of that theory.
Oh. now I'm a theory?
No. you're not.
You're not a theory.
You're very much real.
You're actually...
I'm shocked
this is even happening.
Look. you're cute.
good cook and a better kisser.
but the $40 body wash. that's
the reason I'm sitting here.
Sixty-seven.
Oh. Well. that makes me
like you even more.
Can we shift gears?
Back to bed?
Different gear.
I want to get you in front
of the president and principal
and walk them through
getting this well producing.
Well. I can walk them through
getting it drilled.
but I-I can't guarantee
it'll produce.
But you said drilling for gas
was more forgiving.
It is.
If the reservoir is proven.
Now. this-this is a wildcat.
I mean. there is gas
in the region.
This is a very likely
spot for it.
but there's no guarantees
for that.
We know where
- the well produced.
- Right.
Well. it stopped
producing because it blew out.
Because of a hurricane.
Hurricanes are on the surface.
The well is 30.000 feet below.
I... I need
a no-bullshit assessment.
What are the odds
that we reach the gas field?
Well. look. I've glanced
at the seismics.
and I need to study
the reservoir.
- check the production history...
- What are the odds?
Ten percent.
We are spending
$400 million on this drill.
You know. diamonds aren't
expensive because they're rare.
They're expensive
because they're hard to find.
It's the same with our business.
Look. I'm the very best
at what I do.
If there's gas in that field.
I will find it.
Just give me time to glance
over the seismics. and...
- Sounds like a guarantee.
- Mm-mmm. It's a belief.
I need more than a belief.
I can't give you that.
Anyone who says that they can
is lying to you. You know.
Wildcatting... it's a belief
and nothing else.
I don't know
what wildcatting means.
It's risking it all.
Chips to the middle.
Fortune or failure. caution
to the wind. All on a hunch.
That well produced for eight
years. We know gas is there.
You know gas is there.
Then the well blew.
started pumping water.
Did the pocket collapse?
Were you in a small reservoir?
Were you on the edge
of a big one?
I mean. production
had little decline.
Hints at a big one.
but you don't know.
That's wildcatting.
Now. you can take
all your money to Vegas
and get better odds.
but if these hit.
you're not measuring in MCFs.
you're measuring in TCFs.
I don't know TCF.
Rebecca. you work
for an oil company.
How can you not know
what a TCF is...
I'm not a petroleum geologist.
I'm a fucking
litigation attorney.
You are the geologist.
so would you be so kind as to
tell me what the fuck a TCF is?
A million cubic feet. MCF.
Trillion cubic feet. TCF.
An MCF of natural gas
trades at 375.
so...
you do the math.
'cause I can't count that high.
But if it misses...
- we're out $400 million.
- Yeah.
That's wildcatting.
It's Saturday. man. Shit.
Man. don't anybody
want to just sleep in
on the weekends in this camp?
Got to go cruise Clements.
Show off their rides.
chase honeys.
All the money they got
in those fucking things.
they better do something
with 'em.
Hey. you ever go down there?
Hell no.
This car culture deal
never made it
to the reservation.
We run eight deep
in a 30-year-old van
and don't give a fuck.
Might blow three paychecks
on a horse.
but not a damn car.
What time's
Boss want us over there?
- Whenever you're ready.
- I'm ready now.
Let's get on the road
before we get stuck
behind 50 of these things.
Oh. shit. They're about to move.
Out of the way!
Hey. don't spray gravel
on these guys. they'll shoot us.
Woo!
Hey. motherfucker!
Everyone's so quiet.
November. five. five.
niner. kilo. golf.
All right. Love you. honey.
I'll see you this afternoon.
You got to really make one mad
to get the finger
as she's climbing
on your fucking jet.
- Love you. Daddy.
- Love you. baby.
I'll try to smooth things over.
That's a job for time
and tequila. honey.
Well. luckily. jets have both.
God works in mysterious ways.
What did you do?
Well. I'll tell you this. uh...
not even as a joke...
don't ever put your dick
in a woman's omelet.
To be honest. son. the thought
has never crossed
my fucking mind.
Hey.
- Hey. guys.
- How we doing. Jaqui?
How are you?
I'm so good. how are you?
Oh. hey. good to see you.
Good to see you.
Y'all come on in.
All right.
We got wives in the living room.
Barbecue and beer
is out back. Wives?
Hello. wives.
How y'all doing? Yeah.
How are you?
Baby. you need anything?
Oh. I'll take some more waters.
please. baby.
- Water. you got it.
- Thank you.
Glad to see y'all breathing.
man. That was some bullshit.
Yeah. I don't want
to live it again.
Man. they took Jerrell home
in a wheelchair.
He blind as a motherfucker.
Praying that's temporary.
- You and me both.
- Yeah.
- Hey. Boss.
- Oh. BR.
- King. what's up. man?
- What's up. brother?
- Hey. I hope y'all hungry.
- Oh. we're hungry.
What you got there?
Damn. Who got a birthday?
It's my 20 year bonus.
Yeah.
We all kings today. brother.
Hey. grab y'all a plate
and a beer.
- Yeah.
- How you like yours. BR?
I'll take mine rare.
Oh. that's that bloodthirsty
Viking shit right there.
How about you. King?
Man. I'm a Comanche.
You already overcooked mine.
Here. Unless you want to grab
a raw one right out the cooler.
Don't tempt me.
I'm gonna eat mine before it
gets up and runs off. all right?
Enjoy it. man.
I'll be over there in a minute.
Hey. you.
- Jaqui. Jaqui. Jaqui. Hello.
- Come on inside.
How are you?
I'm good. We got the boys
outside in the back. okay?
Okay. All right.
What... Is that for me?
Everything I have
is yours. Jaqui.
Come here.
You look great. sweetheart.
Thank you. You too.
It is unfair to humanity
that he gets you all to himself.
I swear to God.
You can go fight him over me.
- we can run away together.
- I fucking will.
- And I'll fight dirty.
- Great.
All right. They're out back.
What are the men
doing outside? I mean.
here's the party. Shit.
Word is you're single again.
Well. you know what?
Yall need new hobbies
if that's the latest gossip.
But. uh. yes. I'm on the market.
So. uh. if y'all know any.
you know. swimsuit models
with terrible taste in men.
just send 'em my way.
I have a swimsuit.
Okay.
Dale!
- You made it.
- Hey. buddy.
- What's happening. man?
- Hey. walk with me. will you?
- Oh. yeah. Watch the food.
- Talk to you about something.
- Come here.
- Oh. shit.
the Boss' boss is here.
Oh. shit. I ain't nobody's boss.
Quiet.
Happy 20.
Oh. really? I-I thought
this was just for the suits.
You make it 20. you make it 20.
Aw...
Ooh.
Yeah.
Now. they call that. um.
the Daytona Panda.
- Holy shit.
- Get a look at that.
Thank you. man.
Now. you thank Tommy. okay?
He wanted to be here
but he got called to Fort Worth.
so...
Could sell that thing
and retire.
No. you couldn't retire. King.
But you. uh. you could
buy a pretty nice boat.
Think of all the ways
that this job can kill you.
The busts.
Man camps.
Hell. we stayed in tents when
we were drilling in Oklahoma.
Outrunning tornados. blowouts...
I'm shocked I'm still here. man.
Yeah. yeah. but. uh...
it put a daughter
through college. didn't it?
Nice house for that pretty wife
who don't have to work.
Yeah. I know all that.
Dale. but...
I just don't think
I have 20 more in me.
Hell. I ain't
got two more in me.
- Yeah.
- Been feeding that 401K
like a hunting dog.
That's the trick. ain't it?
Take what you can from
this place and then get out.
- Get the fuck out.
- Yes. sir.
Well. I don't know what y'all
give for 21 years.
but I ain't gonna be around
to find out.
After this summer.
you want to see me. you got to
come out there to Houston. baby.
Uh-huh.
Looks good on you.
- Look at that. Uh-huh.
- Who wants a beer?
- Oh. shit. I'll take one.
- Yeah. I'll take one. too.
Here. Dale.
- Thank you. sir.
- Let's go.
- Appreciate it.
- You bet.
So. what about you. Dale...
when you getting out?
It's. uh. oh. shit.
it's different for me.
Yeah.
I'm a treasure hunter.
It ain't a job for me.
If it ain't a job. what is it?
It's an addiction.
It is.
Now we're being honest.
Goddamn. son.
I know I'm not long
for this world.
but I don't need to die today.
Slow down!
The safest place on this road's
in front of these fucking semis.
We don't want to be behind
these sons of bitches
going up Ranger Mountain.
I need to find a bathroom.
We haven't been on the road
an hour yet.
I don't care how long
we been on the road.
Unless you want me pissing
- on the floorboard...
- Goddamn it.
it's like taking a fucking
road trip with Angela.
I can't wait till
your prostate is the size
of a fucking grapefruit.
I guess you'll clothespin
your dick closed so you don't
- wet your fucking pants.
- Son of a...
You happy?
Not yet.
Ain't that my fucking luck?
Go ahead.
Put me out of my misery.
You need anything else...
you want a blankie
or a sippy cup or something?
I wouldn't say no to lunch.
Pop. you think
you could eat a little faster?
'Cause if you don't. your lunch
is gonna turn into supper.
I like to enjoy my food.
Unlike you.
who sucks it down
like a fucking catfish.
Don't smoke while I'm eating.
Goddamn it.
What's your hurry. son?
All those problems
you're racing home to fix
is problems when you get there.
And once you solve 'em.
there's a whole new set
right behind 'em.
You got to enjoy the moments
between the problems.
Otherwise...
problems is all you'll have.
You know. it's funny...
I don't recall that philosophy
when you were climbing
inside of a whiskey bottle
after filing a missing persons
report on my mother.
I didn't know it then.
You take a long.
hard look at me.
I am the road map
to living life wrong.
Whatever time I got left.
I'm gonna enjoy.
This steak.
That sweet tea.
A dance with your wife.
That granddaughter's smile.
You got it all. son.
But you're too fucking stupid
to see it.
Or too mad.
Or too addicted to the fix.
Whatever it is.
you're missing it.
I'll be in the truck.
Here you go.
I'll bring the change.
Change is for the waitress.
Got you a little T-shirt there?
Yeah. and a couple of cups.
There's a truck stop in Abilene
where you can go act like
a California tourist and
take a picture with a jackalope.
You want to go there?
Lead the way. son.
Why'd you call him?
- I got to give him something.
- Hey. Mom.
Hi. baby.
I'm so excited!
Oh...
This piece of shit
have any air conditioning?
It does.
Doesn't have any Freon.
Mama. don't touch anything.
Probably puts his boogers
underneath the dashboard.
There you go. baby.
I polished it.
- Oh. God. you stink.
- Thanks. Mom.
- She's gonna be so happy.
- I didn't know there was
- a breakfast sausage cologne.
- Ainsley.
Just a little deodorant
could go a long way. honey.
And a shower.
- Ainsley.
- In a vat of acid.
Oh. just be nice.
It's a big day
for him and his little familia.
We got to start planning.
We got to pick a church.
we need a location
for the reception.
Have you thought about
choosing your best man?
First he needs to make a friend.
Maybe I should ask first.
before we start planning.
Yeah. she could still
come to her senses and say no.
Besides. it's the bride's family
that plans the wedding.
not the groom's.
Groom's family
plans the rehearsal dinner.
and that's her last
real chance to leave you.
Oh. my Go... Mom!
That's enough.
- Or I will twist.
- Okay!
Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's like when a bull sees red.
it can't help but attack.
That's what his stink
does to me.
Yeah. you know. I'm s-I'm sure
you got every inch
of your wedding planned.
Course I do. Wedding's gonna be
at St. Andrew's
in downtown Fort Worth.
the reception at the barn
at Circle T Ranch.
You and Daddy
need to start making friends
with Ross Perot Jr..
'cause it is...
it's real expensive.
You wonder why I hate him.
Were we meeting today?
We are now.
Can I come in?
Please.
You want to have a seat?
- I'm too upset to sit.
- Upset about what?
I met with Charlie.
Charlie?
Offshore driller?
I thought he went by Charles.
He introduced himself
as Charlie.
Oh. To me. it's always been
Charles. Interesting.
Not that interesting.
And not relevant.
He says that there's no
guarantee that the drill site
will successfully
strike the gas field.
Well. there's never
any guarantees.
So many issues
could impede success.
He's not talking about
impeding success.
He says the likelihood
that we are successful
is ten percent.
Well. that's wrong. Our
success rate on land is higher.
and horizontal fracking
an almost certainty.
- but still...
- He seemed pretty certain.
That was producing
before the hurricane.
That is number two.
Hurricane didn't
cause the blowout.
The timing was a coincidence.
Then what caused it?
This is starting
to make more sense.
Monty weighed the odds
between drilling and litigating
and decided
he had better odds in court.
If we refuse to drill.
how would you fight this?
Look. I don't know
how Monty convinced them
to pay the claim directly.
but neither do the plaintiffs.
If they did.
they would have presented that
or at least declared it
in the court filings.
That's their case.
As it stands. all we have is
an insurance company
that altered its own policy
with no damages.
The insurance company is
spending 400 million regardless.
Okay.
I think we litigate.
The goal being dragging it out
as long as possible
until we recover the money
from the funds
or the workovers are online
and we can pay out a settlement.
And I need this before a jury.
I don't need a mediator
applying logic here. I need 12
blue collar workers
who will equate this
to getting in a car wreck
and the insurance company
sending the check to them
instead of the bank.
I'll write up
a change of venue request.
I'll notify
plaintiff's attorneys.
Don't notify anyone.
I need Charles
to explain this to Tommy.
and then we all need
to explain this to Cami.
and she will be harder
to convince than a judge.
Well. I'll get
everything prepared.
When we have the green light.
I'll pull the trigger.
I'm just printing out
something for you to sign.
What am I signing?
It's a...
conflict form.
And what is the conflict?
A romantic relationship
with a coworker
who is your subordinate?
Nobody calls him Charlie.
Is it your position
that there is
no romantic relationship?
I would not say romantic.
Would you say sexual?
Charles will
need to sign as well.
And the indignity continues.
There is no indignity
and there is no judgement here.
Fine.
I'll take it to him.
That could be perceived
as coercion.
Please.
This goes on my record.
If I'd slept with him.
I'd be the one
signing it
and it would go on my record.
I'm just looking out for
the best interests
of the company. Rebecca.
So now you
present it to the board.
Correct.
Well played. Counselor.
- I'm not playing.
- Yeah. I can see that.
Oh. God.
Hi. Rebecca.
There's my little
pirate's wench.
Mm. love you.
Thanks. Mom.
Thank you.
I swear.
that girl is wound tighter
than Dick's hatband.
Yeah.
Do you mean like a cock ring?
Honey. get your head
out of the gutter.
No.
Dick was a king
whose crown didn't fit.
There was a king named Dick?
Dick is short for Richard.
Oh. goodness.
let me tell you. honey.
somewhere. back in the old days.
there was a man named Richard
who went by Dick
and must have been hung like
a Georgia plow mule.
It cooling off at all out there?
Eh. not much.
It's not even June.
How can I help you. hon?
I-I'm needing some roses.
Okay. How many?
How much are they?
Uh. well. it depends on
which ones
and the type of arrangement.
Well. I-I don't really
need an arrangement.
I'm... really just need
the flowers.
I'm thinking
a little more volume-driven.
Oh. like petals in the tub.
that kind of thing?
Uh. mine's just
more of a trail of roses.
Oh.
Well. you know what?
I have a shipment.
it's a little past its prime.
but there's a pile of 'em and I
can let you have 'em for cheap.
Say. two dollars a stem?
Yeah. o-okay.
I'll take a hundred.
Okay. come on back.
I'll show you.
We're home. Pop.
Hey. Pop. wake up. we're home.
Hey. Pop. wake up.
- Hey. we're home.
- What the fuck?!
Goddamn!
The fuck the matter with you?
I tried to wake you up
three fucking times.
Pulling on my fucking mustache.
I'm gonna have to get you
one of them ear trumpets.
- like the English wear.
- Yeah. fuck you.
Good God almighty.
What you doing sneaking around
the neighborhood?
Are you all right?
Did somebody die or something?
I had sex
with one of your geologists.
I thought you should
hear it from me.
Okay.
Well. what do you
want me to say.
"Nice job. way to go.
how was it"?
I don't... I-I...
What are you looking for here?
I signed the conflict
disclosure form
and I just...
I want you to consider
what I've accomplished
for this company.
I don't give a shit
who you jump in the sack with.
I really don't.
It violates
the workplace conduct...
Are you shitting me?
Did you ever go to
man camp on a Friday night?
They're running girls and booze
and God knows what else
in and out of that place
like it's a fucking cattle sale.
The whole place
is a workplace violation.
So. this guy
does a really good job...
and you catch him
fooling around or whatever.
you don't fire him.
Now. this guy does a bad job.
you have to fire him
no matter how much you like him.
Deal?
Deal.
Okay.
Hey. by the way.
Saturday night
is typically taco night.
and there's no dress code.
so if you're hungry...
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
Thank you.
Hey. Rebecca.
Who had you sign this paper?
Nathan.
Oh. thank you.
Just one.
I wish every night
was taco night.
It is. 300 miles south of here.
Hey. bud. you want a beer?
- Yeah. sure.
- Is that Tommy?
Yeah. hi. honey.
Can I have a word
with you. Nate?
You sure you want
to poke this bear?
It is a workplace
violation. Tommy.
She works 12 hours a day.
I mean. where is she gonna meet
somebody if it's not at work?
You think she's gonna
find the man of her dreams
at the damn Patch Cafe?
- Be that as it may...
- Look. there are
a lot of people
I don't mind calling enemies.
She is not one of 'em.
And you don't want her
laying awake all night
trying to figure out
ways to get your ass back.
It goes to deeper issues
we're facing. Tommy.
You know what.
I don't want to talk about it.
I'm off the clock.
and from now on.
starting today.
I'm gonna enjoy my life.
You ain't enjoying life today.
You can eat it or fuck it.
I don't really care.
Come on. Come with me.
Let's go take a walk.
You know what I realized today?
What a gift it is
to have you back in my life.
You're a beautiful tornado
of a gift. honey.
And I know I damn sure
don't deserve it.
Damn sure don't.
But I got it.
I just want to thank you for it.
I love you. honey.
You didn't say anything
about my tits.
They're a perk.
I can't lie to you.
I just want to be loved.
You are.
And wanted.
Oh. you are.
And worshipped.
All of it. honey.
You got all of it.
And showered with gifts
and a house in Fort Worth
and something on the beach.
I'm a Pisces. baby.
You know. I'm just...
I'm a little fish
who's stranded ashore.
I'm on it.
Now can I have a taco?
Oh. you can have a taco.
you sexy son of a bitch.
They're the only
grown-ups I know
that love and laugh and...
and they kiss like teenagers.
Why is that?
I'm not sure
"grown-up"
is the right term
for their behavior.
I ain't never seen
nothing like it.
Maybe that's the secret.
Never grow up.
This is it. isn't it?
Where do you want me?
Uh. b...
Just... follow the roses.
Why are you so nervous?
I already said
we should do this.
Well. I've just noticed
this pattern
of you changing your mind
pretty quickly.
I don't change my mind.
Circumstances change
and I change with them.
Circumstances
are always gonna change.
But I won't.
The way I feel right now. I...
it will never...
Forever's a long time.
No.
No. i-it'll be over
before we know it.
So we better not waste a second.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-